<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Volunteer</string>
    <string name="app_splash">Volunteer</string>
    <string name="app_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_volunteering_history">Volunteering History</string>
    <string name="app_faqsText">FAQs</string>
    <string name="app_registerText">Register</string>
    <string name="app_loginText">Login</string>

    <string name="app_faq">
    <![CDATA[

    <b>Q: What is the purpose of the volunteering app?</b>
    <br>
       A: The volunteering app is designed to connect individuals who
       are interested in volunteering with local organizations and events
       that need volunteers. The app allows users to browse and sign up for volunteer
       opportunities, track their volunteer hours, and connect with other like-minded
       individuals in their community.
    <br><br>

    <b>Q: How do I sign up for the volunteering app?</b>
       <br>
       A: To sign up for the volunteering app, simply download the app from the App Store or
       Google Play Store, and create an account using your email address or social media account.
       Once you have created an account, you can start browsing and signing up for volunteer opportunities
       in your area. <br><br>

    <b>Q: How do I find volunteer opportunities near me?</b><br>
       A: Once you are logged into the app, you can use the search function to find volunteer
       opportunities near you. You can filter the results by location, date, type of opportunity,
       and more. Additionally, the app will recommend volunteer opportunities based on your interests
       and previous volunteer experience.
    <br><br>

    <b>Q: Can I track my volunteer hours using the app?</b> <br>
        A: Yes, the volunteering app allows you to track your volunteer hours for each
        opportunity you participate in. You can view your total volunteer hours, as well as a
        breakdown of hours by organization and event, in the "My Volunteer Hours" section of the app.
        <br><br>

    <b>Q: Can I use the app to sign up for volunteer opportunities as a group?</b> <br>
        A: Yes, the app allows you to sign up for volunteer opportunities as a group. When signing
        up for an opportunity, you can indicate the number of volunteers in your group, and the app
         will reserve spots for all members of your group. Please note that some volunteer opportunities
         may have a limit on the number of volunteers they can accommodate.

    ]]>


    </string>
</resources>